Help
Xiaoyu, are you okay?
I'm fine, just in case, brother, you
I'm fine, run away
how about you
Hum I'm a waste
you are different
Coming of Age Ceremony Tomorrow
You can awaken the dragon soul
Can
But
OK
Yeah
ah
This mouth looks so stinky
Pity me, what if I die before I even get a wife?
Brother Billion
Ah, Sister Bai Wuxia
Xiaoyu, don’t be alone in this wilderness from now on
very dangerous
Sister Bai, I understand
This time, thanks to brother Wan Yi
let's go back
Bring Brother Wan Yi with you
Tomorrow is the fame ceremony. You need to go back quickly to prepare.
Sister Bai, put me down quickly. I want to save Brother Wan Yi.
If you care so much
I'll just come back and pick him up later.
Don’t worry, my remaining dragon spirit is here
The wild beasts dare not approach
Legend has it that tens of thousands of years ago
There is a paradise
There are many dragons living there
The steamer needs to absorb a lot of steam
Causes the earth’s air to become thinner
Secrets of Humanity on the verge of extinction
to save humanity
The survivors made weapons to fight the dragon
Start killing the dragon
The dragons are running around
The last giant dragon escaped to the Central Plains
Seal the dragon clan's hope underground
The energy erupted when the dragon died filled the air
Practitioners call it Dragon Soul
I don’t know what happened to Brother Yiyi, Xiaoyu
Uncle Wanchi
Xiaoyu, you came here so early, eh?
Today is the coming of age ceremony
I'm very nervous, so come here early.
Relax, your soul power is already at the beginning level
no problem
Well, thank you, Uncle Wanchi, by the way.
I didn’t watch it last night in case I come back
I thought he was with you, huh?
nothing came back
Didn't Sister Bai say she would go back to pick her up?
For today’s coming-of-age ceremony, you two need to work together.
I thought you would come together
How to do how to do
What if I don't die in the dark forest?
Forget it, that brat has no soul power anyway.
Even if you take the test, it will be a useless test.
It's my fault
It killed Brother Wan Yi
Sorry, Uncle Wanchi
Literary brother
Why
Shouting so loudly to summon spirits?
What if you're not dead, brother?
Hey, don't, don't, don't
I can’t die before my wife is married.
What about Sister Bai?
Didn't I come back with you?
No, I woke up and found that you were all gone, so I came back on my own.
I felt relieved when Menfang said you were back.
Yo who is this?
Why do you have the face to appear here?
Hum little trash
You can come to such a sacred place as the Dragon Soul Palace
Hurry up and get out of here
i have a name
Brother Wansen, sister Wanlin, don’t do this
Little girl, you have no place to speak here.
You seem very unconvinced
Our Wan family has produced numerous talents over the past hundred years.
How come our generation has a piece of trash like you?
if it weren't for your father
A burden like you would have been kicked out of Wanjia long ago.
Why do you still want to fight?
Who can you beat?
Just to piss you off
In this way, we can legitimately wake up this waste
Hum, I'll fight you
Okay, then I’ll teach you a lesson too
I have time to laugh at others here
It’s better to spend more time cultivating your soul
Sister Bai is so nice
Hum, she's just a foreign girl
What's there to be proud of?
Who are you showing your face to?
My sister is merciful
Wanjia respects strength
It's understandable that he is arrogant.
Humph, who is a family member with him?
Do you think I can't see through those frivolous things of yours?
Sister, what are you talking about?
The adult secret begins soon
What's going on with Sister Bai?
When I returned last night, I couldn't find it.
Such a serious injury
He actually recovered in one night
Today is our annual coming-of-age ceremony
according to rules
Today, the 16-year-old Wan will be tested for his soul power.
Shiyu and 18-year-old Wanyi
Just in case, this is the third soul power test your father has fought for for you.
Also the last time
You have to cherish it
Father, let's start.
Wan Shiyu comes first
It's Uncle Wan Zhang
It’s the Dragon Soul of the Three Realms
Not bad?
It’s one level higher than you were before.
Yeah, the natural charm attribute
It's a good seedling
The next coming-of-age ceremony is a coat where the soul power cannot be measured for two years.
No, no
Relax and don't be stressed
Cheer for Brother Yi
I believe you can
It has been three years, even for the lowest level Dragon Soul
Please let me wake up this time
Ask for help
ah
farted
Look at the salted fish, it’s the salted fish
Father, you have to consider our suggestions.
Although my father said that there was also a little loser in the Xiao family, the engagement was annulled.
But if they know that I, the Wanjia family, also have one
Or is it your hostility?
How can I save your face?
What the second brother said is not unreasonable.
two seniors
Can you be more polite when speaking in front of grandpa?
How dare you kid talk back?
If it's not for someone's sake
I will destroy you with one palm
You are a loser anyway
Ouch
You also heard that it’s not that grandpa won’t keep you
This is the birth of the Wan family over the past hundred years
You can't destroy it in the hands of me, Wan Tianba.
Just because I have no soul power
So you don’t even have the qualifications to stay in Wanjia?
Although you have no soul power
After all, they are my Wan family members
It's not very humane to kick you out like that.
But Wanjia’s reputation is also very important
You need to understand grandpa’s difficulties later.
I see
No, you don’t understand yet
There are only two roads before you now
The first is to leave Wanjia and fly away
incognito
Second, there is a bottomless pit deep in the Dragon Soul Ruins.
called Longming Cave
Legend has it that a purple plant, Longyinhua, grows in the cave.
If you can step on it and take it, you can generate fame in your body.
The fame itself is the power of dragon soul
So it is also possible to reshape the physical body
Forging Dragon Soul
Since it is a bottomless pit
How is it possible for plants to grow?
So this is just a legend
The legend is that I don’t know whether it is true or not
No one has ever been to Longmyeongdong.
Even if you go, you won't be able to come back alive.
Even if you can live
We may not be able to find the legendary Long Minghua either.
So hum
yeah
Ah, one son and one brother
Wanchi
Father may leave here
It’s good for you and him
Hahaha, hurry up and find a place to kill yourself, you little loser.
Wanzhang, I want to duel with you
The gun is for a loser. You think I'm afraid of you?
enough
Still think my Wan family is not chaotic enough?
Ah, this matter has passed like this
Not to be mentioned again
Everybody stand down
where are you going
leave me alone
Are you planning to leave like this and be looked down upon for the rest of your life?
You'll be looked down upon if you stay here anyway.
Where is your dignity?
Where was your courage when you rescued me?
Humorous
Do I have dignity?
I don't care if you're still a man
Just stay
Cultivate your soul and show it to them
Never been a man
Huh, loser
Just think I misjudged you
Although I don’t believe there is any dragon singing flower
But I still came here unknowingly
Maybe it's because I'm homeless
I just looked at you and felt sad
I didn't expect it to be so cold
Where is the entrance to this cave?
Grandpa only said that he was in the ruins
Didn't say the specific location
What a careless grandpa
regenerate
If you don't find the entrance to the cave, I will freeze to death here first.
The father and the child are unfilial
Have you grown up here?
It feels so dangerous here
You won't hang up as soon as you enter, right?
There must be something ferocious about this voice
Just hang it on the wall.
I'm not a fool
Come in
Isn't this an illusion caused by freezing?
No matter what, let's go and take shelter from the wind.
It's better than freezing to death here.
Oh, much warmer
Is this the farmer's cave?
Although it's pretty
But it’s not like a bottomless pit.
Will peasant flowers grow in a place like this?
Peasant flowers Peasant flowers Peasant flowers
Where do farmers spend their money?
wrong
What does the farmer's flower look like?
Well, go back and ask grandpa
Where is the exit?
let me out
oops
I never thought that I would be a coward for the rest of my life.
In the end, I had to starve to death in this cave.
Not even the body was found.
Father and child are unfilial
Mother
The child will be with you soon
Help
What a powerful micro-pressure
What I felt from my grandfather before was the most powerful slight pressure in my life.
But not as good as 1/10,000 at this moment. What kind of monster is it?
Ahhh
and all
where is this
am i dead
you are not dead
I'm afraid only Sister Bai can be compared to the world in her beauty.
But this one looks younger
Wow this is my thing hahaha
Leader, I have been waiting for you for tens of thousands of years
Hahaha lady
Please excuse me quickly
Dragon Lord for tens of thousands of years
monster
Dragon Lord
This will make orchids grow
Anyway, thank you for your hard work over the years.
I've given you back what's yours
something that belongs to me
ah
This is the gray dragon soul
No, I finally have a dragon soul.
Well, now your dragon soul has been blessed by my dragon weapon
I owe you my soul
I've given it back to you a hundredfold
Dragon weapon dragon soul
I originally had a dragon soul
You said that the thing that belongs to me is the dragon soul
Um
Wanjia’s dragon soul is a little stronger
Blessed by my dragon energy
Will be more feminine
Feminine, I am a man
Not suitable
When you think it's appropriate
You are a man
a ha ha ha
Even you said I'm not a man hahaha
Oh, right
What is a dragon weapon?
It's a long story
I'll explain it to you later
I didn’t expect that when you lost your dragon soul, you also lost your dignity.
turn out to be
This is my dragon soul
That's right
What I lost was my dignity
One or two
Now I give you the dragon soul
As for dignity, you need to take it back yourself
can i get it back
The original poster
Call me just in case
Although I don’t know why you called me that
But this title sounds quite awkward, right?
What do you call it?
i have no name
Qinglong, if you can call me Qinglong
Qinglong, you said you have been waiting for me for tens of thousands of years
Are you alive?
Um
Have we ever heard of the ancient dragon clan?
The ancient dragon tribe 100,000 years ago
human ancestors
Impossible impossible
That's just a legend
Could it be that it's a dragon's roar?
Your dragon soul is infused with a dragon weapon
It’s not comparable to ordinary dragon souls either.
With this Wanlongjue
Your skills will improve by leaps and bounds
This is the horse flower and the farmer's flower
Please take back your dignity
Wanjia, I'm back
Xiaoyu is right
I can't just leave like this
Madam, wasn’t this good-for-nothing kicked out of the house three years ago?
Why are you back?
So what if I come back?
It’s not like living like a dog
if i were him
Just find a gun and pretend to be dead.
That's it
It's exactly as expected.
If it were before
I should be so angry that I can grit my teeth.
It turned out that only 3 days had passed
There is no sense of time in the secret realm
I thought it had been a long time
Is something wrong with the two tigers of the mountain?
I knew you, a loser, wouldn't be able to survive outside for a few days.
Sure enough, wouldn’t he just come back with his tail between his legs?
Hahahahahaha
I have something to ask you to get out of my way
Hey, this dog can talk.
It's okay to go there
Get under my crotch
I don't want to say it again
Please get out of the way
What if you come back, brother?
Granny Wan Shai and I are very worried about you.
Waste is waste
He only hides behind women
Xiaoyu, I'm sorry to make you worry.
Let's go back
Aren't you going to let me go?
Whatever you say today, you have to get under my crotch
Don't bully others too much
It's not your crab's turn to point fingers.
They are not qualified
And me
Brother Sen is here
This guy is going to be woken up again
Hahahahahahahaha there’s something good to watch
Little waste, I thought you had been snatched away by jackals, tigers and leopards.
Hahahahahaha
How can jackals, tigers and leopards compare to you beasts?
You little loser, how dare you talk to us like this?
It seems that the skin is itchy again
Today, I will teach you a lesson on behalf of my family.
Don't be afraid, Xiaoyu
When we leave, we will call him a dog that doesn’t bite people.
court death
careful
Xiaoyu
Trash, someone will always protect you
If you are a man, stand up for yourself
Sure enough, you won't get respect if you just fight head on.
Fight if you want
That's fine. I know you're unhappy on weekdays.
Today I will give you a chance to raise your head
Do you dare to hold the stage?
Unexpected
snort
Hum God Mysterious
It’s nothing more than repeating the message
Today I will let you shoot yourself in the foot
What
Ye'er is back
Still want to compare with 10,000 to 5?
Third brother, third brother
Your son finally has sex for once
It's a pity that he wants to challenge my son
After today, he will live worse than a dog
you
snort
Hahaha
Suppress it, suppress it
One level pays 100 fast
Just because he dared to accept Brother Sen's challenge without reincarnation, I admire him very much. Of course, that's right.
Then next time, Brother Sen will be confused and ridden by his Lushan ghost for three days, unable to get out of bed.
Now I’m not afraid even thinking about it
What are you looking at, little loser?
Is it my future wife you want to see when you ask her to?
If you think closing the stage is fighting with your mouth or simply admitting defeat, forget it.
Look how big your row is
Almost everyone from the Wan family has arrived
Today, in front of everyone, I will clean up the expenses of your electric family honor.
But brother, I have a good heart
It's okay to leave your body intact
Without further ado
Let's do it
There are so many people in the audience
We can't let people down
Raise the stakes
Whoever loses will cut off his arms
Why are you so scared?
You're wrong. I mean since everyone wants us to play bigger.
Better to up the ante
How about destroying the dragon soul?
Ahhhhh
Laowei
Which part of your body is wrong?
Why are you still humiliating yourself?
This guy can't be serious about such details, right?
He must be a fat man with a long face
Do not make jokes
You don’t even have a dragon soul
What are you betting on me?
It's just too shameless
Why don't you go down?
You do not dare
Like jade and nature for three lifetimes
Even if it is an unequal bet, he will definitely accept it.
Ha ha
Why don’t I dare to laugh?
Do you think you have half a chance of winning?
So what if I let you
Why
Fund Wansan is very fast in making moves
But when you join the Longminghua team, you can even see clearly the Ghost Festival.
Alas
Oops
This body technique looks young
But he was able to escape Wansen’s offensive.
I've never seen such dark hair
Ask for help
Wow come on wow
You little loser, can you just hide?
snort
I wanted to play with him, but I didn't expect to be stabbed.
It depends on how long you hide
Hey Dragon God Legs
This is hey
ah
Wow come on
Wow
The unbridled flow of blood covers the ears
Knock down the opponent as quickly as possible before the opponent can react
The characteristic of the blue dragon soul is that it has an endless supply of energy.
In addition, the Dragon God’s legs are famous for their speed
Most people can't stand this kind of combination. Only if they understand this trash can they dare to save their own face.
I'll deal with you right away
ah
That
I actually have a dragon soul
No wonder he dares to be so confident
Dragon soul?
How did he rise to the dragon soul?
Yes, when I saw Hei Buliuqiu’s appearance, Eryinghun was so scared that I died.
Never seen it before
good
Although I don’t know how he awakened his soul
While he just woke up
Destroy him and never cause further trouble
Do you think you can defeat me if you have soul power?
Five words for you
Too stupid and too naive
Knowing these five words, I will return them to you intact.
King Kong Dragon Divine Legs
Force Brother Sen to use this trick
Even if you die, it's an honor
ah
elder brother
It's impossible how could this guy be so powerful?
He has just gotten close to the dragon soul
As soon as I take action, you will be gone
The two words you often call me are returned to you in a round and round manner, and that’s all you are.
you
waste
ah
Shenlongjue
What kind of move is this?
grandson
Brother um
How is it possible? How is it possible? What happened to him?
What should I do if I am kicked out of the team, Master?
waste
How dare you kill me
ah
Ah, I'll just say it
In case you finally do it
Brother Yi is great
Just got on the horse
Brother Zhao can't leave.
The grievances of the younger generation of the second brother
It doesn't make sense for you, as an elder, to interfere. Your son beat my son.
I take it out on my son's behalf
get out of my way
Hahahahahaha
They are all dozens of years old
Don't you blush when you say this?
they are a fair duel
Who can you blame if your son is not as good as others?
Second uncle, maybe I was a little harsh.
I thought cousin Wan San was very strong
I didn't expect to be so vulnerable.
you you
ah
Go down
Fortunately, today my grandson’s skills are not as good as others’
in case you win
If I remember this today
let's go
Hey, just leave like that
What else do you want?
Where's the bet?
you
Father
After all, it was Sen'er who proposed the bet.
You can't just default on your debt in front of so many people.
But is it really necessary for Monk to cut off his arms and destroy the dragon soul?
Even with this old face, it's impossible
Everyone is waiting
Young people are easily impulsive
Just a joke
Why take it seriously?
It's not a joke if I lose, right?
I mean, you see, we are all a family.
Keep a line in everything so that we can meet again in the future.
As a family, you are so cruel to ask yourself
Have you ever treated me like a family member over the years?
Let's forget about today's matters
But the insults of the past few years
I think my son needs an apology
Not too much
it's natural
Quickly apologize to my trillion cousin
sorry
snort
cousin
Um
Something happened
Before
Feel sorry
Did he really find Long Minghua?
What a reality
The attitude of everyone in the Wan family towards me has changed 180 degrees.
Stayed alone for a long time
Instead, I can’t blend in with the crowd.
Wan Longjue's secret book made of spiritual energy is very strange.
The exercises are engraved in my mind every moment
No need to practice at all
It will happen naturally
It just consumes my soul power.
The Longming Flower in the body automatically replenishes its own energy for the essence.
forming a virtuous cycle
The previous Shenglongjue suddenly learned it on stage
And what I woke up to was the 9th wedding
Really awesome
Hum the breath of dragon soul
Cidong is a desperate place
How could anyone come?
Taking care of everything with my father-in-law
It's not easy to make a date.
It’s your son, Luo
Could it be that I and my father-in-law are from the imperial court?
There is no need for us to meet too frequently
Hey, this matter is of great importance
Must be used as fabric
Tell me what's going on
Wanlong memorial ceremony will begin
We need to get the new marriage law as soon as possible
New law is in your family when you get married
Wouldn't it be easier for you to succeed?
The soul master’s faith will be enshrined in the Dragon Soul Hall five days before the ceremony.
We three brothers take turns guarding
If morale checks for moles first,
I still have to go to the trouble of taking action with my father-in-law.
Even if I stole the idea
Once you control muddy time
People will also find out
Once you obtain the Dragon Soul inheritance
I am the head of the family
Even Wan Tianba can't do anything to me
The second uncle actually colluded with thousands of people
To seize the position of head of the family
Who has a friend?
Now that you're here, there's no need to be sneaky.
Father-in-law, are you wrong?
If you hadn't arrived in time
I guess I have to explain it above.
thank you
Qinglong
Master, you shoulder the heavy responsibility of reviving the Dragon Clan.
Qilong will definitely protect you
The revival of my dragon clan
Hahaha, stop being ridiculous
To be precise, it’s the jade pendant you’re wearing
This jade pendant
This is what my mother left me
I heard from my father that my mother left on the day I was born.
This matter has to start tens of thousands of years ago
At that time the Dragon Clan
On the run
Hey, wait, wait, wait, hey
I have more important things now
I have to go back quickly and tell grandpa about my second uncle’s conspiracy.
Hey, that blue dragon
Give me a ride
Let's go
ah
Ah ah
Why is it different from last time?
1 Son, this is grandpa
Not good 2
What's wrong
Grandpa is not well
I posted a photo of burping
Hiccups all the time
Are you still hiccupping?
Uh, no, no.
ah
Hahaha I used to hiccup when I was little
Your grandfather also cured me in this way.
Tried and tested
You have to learn this trick
Pass it on well
Got it, thanks grandpa
Uh, then Ye'er should take your leave first.
Hey, what should I do?
I need to tell Grandpa about this as soon as possible.
Why
By the way, go find your father.
If brother is in such a hurry, where will he go?
Xiaoyu, what should I do?
If the second uncle wants to do harm to grandpa, he will do it right away inside.
How to do it
Hey, second uncle, although he is arrogant
But he wouldn't do such a sinful thing.
I heard with my own ears that my second uncle was conspiring with the imperial court to seize the position of head of the family.
Second uncle
Why is it that only the erhu comes out?
grandfather
Why are ghosts crying and wolves howling in broad daylight?
Ah, nothing, nothing
Let's go practice first
Oh no
I have to tell my father
See what can be done
You go back first and wait for news from me.
what can i do
By the way, Sister Bai is so powerful
He will definitely find a way
I'm serious about this
Father
This matter is of great importance
El will never dare to play tricks.
Yeah Ye'er
Never tell anyone else at this time
Father, why is this?
The uncle is straight-tempered
Once I find out, I will definitely ask my second uncle for the theory.
No evidence
I'm afraid it might scare someone off.
then what should we do
Don't worry about this matter
I will go find your grandpa to discuss it.
Are you saying that Wan Zhanglin and the imperial court are trying to seize the title of head of the family?
How did you know
In case brother heard it with his own ears
He has already gone to Uncle Wanchi to discuss countermeasures.
That being the case
No need to panic
I believe your grandpa already knows
The elders will take care of it themselves
The Ten Thousand Dragons Festival will be held in 5 days
How are Wan Yu's preparations?
A little disclosure for my father
Third brother is already helping me deal with it
It will be resolved in just a few days
It will not affect the festival
Do you really have evil intentions?
This soul stone heart method has been passed down from generation to generation by family heads.
I will also pass it on to you in the future.
Father, may you live a long life
It's still early
As expected, this old guy had already planned to pass the joining position to his elder brother.
From now on, this soul stone heart method will be enshrined here.
Wanli and Wanchi are busy offering sacrifices to heaven
Wanchang
You will be responsible for guarding the Dragon Soul Palace these days.
It's the father hahaha
Isn't this move equivalent to giving it away for free?
Zang'er, I hope you won't disappoint your father
Eunuch Yu, don’t worry
This time I kept a careful eye on it
Absolutely no one is following
Yeah, I've also explored this cave.
Except for some little mice and bats
no other signs of life
Father-in-law, this is an excellent opportunity
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
how do I say this
Wanlong Festival is coming soon
Borrowing 100,000 Tianba needs to support the black dragon in person
There will be a period when Xu Ruoqi is a good opportunity for us to take action
Yes, that's the case
Then there’s no need to take the soul master’s mental technique, right?
I don’t know anything about my father-in-law
The key to unlocking the treasure is the soul-testing stone
The soul-measuring stone can only be driven by the soul stone heart method.
And the Black Dragon inheritance can only be activated when looking for food in the ancient reincarnation.
That is the festival day
So we need to get the new law on marriage history in advance
He's obviously the second uncle
But no one believes me because there is no evidence.
Why don't you go talk to my grandpa?
I don’t know your grandfather
Besides, I can’t get out either.
Okay, I'll figure it out myself
I've been waiting for several days, why haven't you come yet?
Have they changed their plans?
Father and children depend on each other for something
come in
Well who?
The little thief has finally waited for you.
drive
Ali ran
Who dares to break into the Dragon Soul Palace at night?
How dare you steal your mind
My father has a thief's mentality
I've been seriously injured
Yuer, why are you here?
Grandpa me
He must be colluding with the thieves
Father, look
Zhang Er
Grandpa, be careful
Ahhh
Miss Mowgli
Right
Are you OK
Brat, let me show you some mercy
I will too
snort
Um
Don't be impulsive
Father, don't worry about which soul master I come first.
Thief
not good
ah
Take your life
Quick defense
father father
do not come
New poisonous
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha...
Help your father heal quickly
A good dog stays out of the way
Little trash, you'd better confess your accomplices.
It was obviously you who colluded with the imperial court to seize the position of the head of the family.
Ridiculous, you stole the mind
Everyone has seen it with their own eyes
Still talking nonsense
I advise you to confess your accomplices as soon as possible
Suffer less
My father's adopted son would never do such a treacherous thing
Hum, of course you will be partial to your own son
In case how to awaken the dragon soul has not yet been explained clearly
Who knows what benefits he received from outsiders?
The second brother’s matter is quite strange.
Still needs careful review
Don’t rush to make a final conclusion
Both witnesses and physical evidence are present
What else can I check?
If you ask me, I should just kill him.
To avoid further trouble
Wan Zhang, don't go too far
The dead don't speak
It's all your words
Enough, close one ear
Let’s discuss it after the sacrifice to heaven
Take this, this is Hunshi's mentality
Hey, I still came to Wantianba with my public reputation.
That old fox wants me to stick to stealing
This time the plan will be calculated
Just in time to help you clean up.
With the soul master's mind
I can activate the Dragon Soul Altar
Once you get the Black Winged Dragon inheritance
I am the legitimate head of the family
Wanjia can only be led by me
Only then can we regain our former glory.
Father's door riot control
The court and father-in-law came to visit
please come up
this outfit
Thief who steals hearts and minds, you still have the nerve to come?
I can say ugly things first
Slandering an important official of the imperial court is a capital offense
But then again
Your boy has helped me a lot.
daughter
The visitor is a guest and is given a seat
Our store has never had anything to do with the imperial court
I didn’t know that my father-in-law and I would come to my humble home today.
What are the instructions?
It's just that we can't talk about it
I heard today is the Ten Thousand Family Festival
My father-in-law is very curious
Came here specially to open my eyes
I don’t know if Wan shop owner would like it or not.
I don’t need to worry about such trivial matters, Mr. Yu.
I think Eunuch Yu must be busy
I won’t leave Wanmou any more.
So anxious to catch up with class
Oh, what a pity
It's not up to you
Feng Huang's mouth
In order to make Eunuch Tianyu personally participate in the memorial ceremony of thousands of families
Wan family members are not allowed to refuse
admire this
Although the Wan family has never obeyed the imperial court's orders,
But after all, it is still within the territory of my court.
Don't do it for a trivial matter
Suffering the disaster of genocide
Shopkeeper Wan, you said this is the reason
Since I am so kind to my father-in-law,
Wan will never refuse
but
If you and your father-in-law dare to disrupt the festival,
Just blame Wan for being ruthless
Isn't that so good?
heard about
The person who won 10 boxes of soft gold umbrellas rashly used his internal power
But it will kill you due to poison
Shameless
Why
ah
Third brother, what does this mean?
Brother, don’t be impulsive
Don't stop me and let me kill this shameless guy
Someone coming
Going down to rest with my father-in-law
snort
Third brother, why did you stop me just now?
Brother, this person has extremely high martial arts skills
Even if you and I work together, we may not be able to win.
What’s more, my father’s toxins are not completely clear yet.
Once a fight breaks out
I'm afraid I'm going to suffer a loss.
snort
What are you afraid of?
Do you want to suffer the loss of being dumb?
Chi'er is right
Wait until the time is right
Seek justice from the court again
In case brother, are you okay?
It's okay. You're in good health.
How could they do this
I arrested you without evidence.
There's no evidence for this yet
He was caught red-handed.
I went there to catch the thief
You know that Uncle Wan Zhang is the one who colludes with outsiders to marry more and become the head of the family.
You're talking nonsense about how my father could do such a thing
Wansan, you have to believe me
I really didn't lie to you
You little waste
No evidence
Don't call the thief here "Catch the thief"
I really have no evidence
But I heard it with my own ears
Your father is going to seize the dragon soul inheritance at the festival
My father has always made family honor his mission
Even if the sky falls
He will not betray Wanjia either
Therefore
For the honor of the family
You must stop your father
Don't let him make the same mistake again and again
What nonsense
After the festival
Someone will take care of you
Xiaoyu, can you do me a favor?
What if, brother, you say
Father
Father, no matter how poisonous you are
Why don't you let your children do it for you?
It's about to start
It's hard to stop Wan Zhang quickly
win together
Spiritual feelings together
The two of them are born from the same roots
Why are you so impatient?
Step aside
Hurry up
Ah you are not good
Wu Song Weiqing could only speed up
Can
Can't let him use Soul Kill
What are you waiting for?
open
not good
snort
What's the use of having the dragon soul come out at your own expense?
ah
burning oracle
Old man, you're crazy
not good
yesi
Wan Tianba is ashamed of his ancestors
Don’t you want to be my date?
Like to die here
Grandpa doesn’t want it
Grandpa
Oops, what should I do?
Oh, right
I can ask Qinglong for help.
But I can't get out now
How to find Qinglong?
Oh, oh, Xiaoyu, you’ll know soon
What are you looking for me for?
This jade pendant can also transmit sounds
It's always been low
do not you know
how would i know
Tell me what you want from me
help me escape
I'm going to stop the second uncle
Start a family legacy
Never
Now the Black Dragon Mutual Breeding Association has matured
Forced inheritance will make the entire Wan family become nutrients for the black dragon
Ah, what should I do?
Once the black dragon forcibly looks for food,
The door to the Dragon Soul Secret Realm will be opened
I will lose the protection of convenience
Isn’t the Dragon Soul Secret Realm in the Dragon Soul Ruins?
What does it have to do with inheritance?
There are two entrances to the secret realm
They were opened and guarded by Black Dragon and Black Dragon respectively.
Nowadays
Only the glorious consciousness in prevention can stop the black dragon
It's all on you
yeah
grandson
Father didn't expect this to be true
Miss, what are you doing?
Xiaoyu, be careful, he is a bad guy
Ah, where will you die?
You can't die
ah
Uncle Wan Zhang
This is not inheritance
It’s the remnant soul of the black dragon
Third brother will die holding on to the iron
Hum, even if I risk my life, I still have to save San'er.
Ahhh
Ah father
Why are you
The Thorny Black Dragon has been evolved by me
won't cause harm to you
Father
Wansen, now you have received the family inheritance
I will inherit your father's agreement from now on.
Be filial and loyal to the court
Why
it's because of you
Ahhh
Sister Bai, let me go quickly
Why did you bring me here?
slay dragon
Slaying the Dragon Where can there be a dragon in this world?
That's just a legend
Have you ever heard of the Dragon Slayers?
I don’t know, please let me go
That's not okay
The show has just begun
Ahhhhhh
Ah ah ah
Everyone knows that pink reincarnation has charm properties
But I don’t know that perception is still the powerful effect of thick powder
The perfect soul power for Xunlong
Hahahahahaha
ah
Dragon slaying tribe
Ahhh
And you little loser
Give me my father
Hard work is dangerous
This road is blocked
Step aside
What if I don’t let you?
At the end of the day you're still a loser
Give birth to a dragon
Bad poster
You can't protect yourself
There is still time to care about others
Aren’t you tired of your dragon-slaying clan chasing us for tens of thousands of years?
Life without dragons is so boring
Hum, it’s rare to meet a little green dragon
You have to have some fun with your sister
I don't have time for you
you are annoying
Dragon slaying
Hum, that's interesting
Why don't you answer?
You blame me for not aiming.
I'm just asking you if you dare to pick it up?
can you try again
ah
Gu Wulong's crime
You liar and coward
Sister, I don’t like this.
If you have the ability, don't move.
ah
Wanlong Town
stand at attention
Wanlong Town is designed to absorb space energy
He will attack as thin as the ground
It is equivalent to capturing energy for Wanlong Town again
This can surpass me
I have to hurry up and earn a trillion dollars a year
uh
Where is Qinglong?
am i dead
This is the space inside the jade pendant
I am communicating with you using dragon soul
Dragon Soul
Haven't my dragon souls been sucked away?
That's right, what I want to help you activate now is the Dragon King's remnant soul.
Back then, the Dragon King took me to escape here
to protect me
The Dragon King split his dragon soul into two
Half draws the enemy away
Leave half of the seal that became this place
The seal is the black dragon
The dragon slayers have found me. I shouldn't be able to escape.
The hope of the Dragon Clan is in your hands
The way to resurrect the Dragon King is in the jade pendant
Jade Dragon Snow
As long as you can
ally
Long live
waste
Fan San, you are from the Wan family
I am
Thousands of Geniuses
What qualifications do you have to say to me, you loser?
I'm a waste
But I want to save Wanjia
I can't even save you
Why do you
Resurrecting the ancient dragon king can save thousands of families
Just a legend
Do you think I will believe you?
I'm not sure either
But I'm willing to bet with my life
do you dare
Why not?
Come on then
The ancestral soul is restored
Look, it’s a dragon
It's a real dragon
Princess
see your meat
hey
Oolong sword
So strong Weiya
Not seen for tens of thousands of years
You forgot how powerful the dragon-slaying sword is
Hey
Wu Longjue
hehe
Quickly use the trick Xiao Longjue
this will make you quickly your nipples
yeah
My my eternity is the new law
Today is the inauguration ceremony of the new head of the family
And starting today, all families will abolish coming-of-age ceremonies.
No longer guarding the Black Dragon Monument
Now, I would like to ask the new head of the family, my brother Wanli, the store manager, to say a few words to you.
applause welcome
Wahahahawahahaha
Dragon Lord, have you decided?
Ah, when I resurrected the Dragon King
I established some kind of connection with Wan Sen
Now I can feel that he is still somewhere in the world
If that's the case
Could it be that Bai Wuxia is also an illusion?
who knows
However, the dragon-slaying sword remained.
Hey Qinglong
Why do you think the Dragon Slayers want to hurt you?
Maybe only they themselves know